Brands lose time when every new asset restarts the same decisions.
Codex Design Studio starts with intent, audience, and outcome.
Reference evidence stays attributed, rights-aware, and reviewable.
GPT-5.6 turns that evidence into one living, versioned Design System.
The polished Web output is directly editable, with stable design nodes and autosave.
Select a real component and ask Codex to change the source—not a mockup.
Before promotion, the Studio renders the candidate and surfaces any regression.
The user keeps the final decision; accepted work remains traceable and reversible.
The same system drives editable presentation scenes, not flattened screenshots.
Export Web, editable PPTX, and tokens from one governed source of truth.